♪♪
From the fire ravaged
community of Southgate.
For most of Atlanta,
this day started out
with the promise of a
clear and sunny spring day.
But in the Southgate community,
that calm was shattered
by the scream of fire
trucks and ambulances
when a four-alarm fire
erupted just hours before dawn.
Engine companies from all over
the city raced to the scene of the fire
but sadly were not able to
prevent extensive property damage.
The pictures of devastation
that you are seeing
are the first to be authorized for
release by the police and fire departments,
due to unusually tight
security in the area.
This is the third large-scale fire in
the Southgate area in the last month.
And like the previous cases,
this fire spread extremely quickly,
hopping from house to
house with terrifying speed.
Many residents of the area were forced
to flee, leaving all possessions behind.
Most of the residents we were able to
speak with were still in a state of shock.
Several others were undergoing
treatment at the Munson Memorial Hospital
for symptoms of shock, smoke
inhalation, and minor injuries.
Many expressed anger at what they
called outside influences and gangs,
whom they blamed for
this spate of recent fires.
A number of residents expressed their
intention to leave the area permanently.
Police officials have
cordoned off an entire area...
It pains me to say
this, Your Honor,
but your ruling
clearly indicates to me
that you are a jackass.
- You said that to his face?
- Right to his face.
My gosh, what did he do?
Oh, he turned as
red as a radish.
He charged me with contempt,
threw me in the
hoosegow for the night,
and reversed his ruling.
- No kidding.
Is it okay to say
"jackass" on TV?
Are you kidding?
Ever since those confirmation
hearings, you can say practically anything.
Jackass, jackass, jackass.
Okay, let's talk about
the Peabody case.
The who case?
The Professor Peabody
triple murder case?
You know, the one where
you represented the geneticist
who was trying to breed
the world's first talking dog?
You don't remember?
No, and I'm sure I would.
Let's talk about the time you
represented those two Russian spies, then.
Russian spies?
Yeah... Boris and Natasha.
Last name Badenov.
- I don't remember them, either.
- Oh, no.
They were accused of
murdering two people...
An R. J. Squirrel
and a B. W. Moose.
Moose and Squirrel?
Yes.
Wait a minute...
B. W. Moose?
Okay. Cut. Damn it.
Doug.
You made me look like a
jackass in front of Ben Matlock.
- Oh, relax, Bill, it's a joke.
- Damn you.
Where's your sense of humor?
You don't get it, Doug.
You and your practical jokes
are going to ruin credibility of
this station's entire news operation.
If you checked out your stories, I
wouldn't have been able to trick you.
But you don't, so I did.
Doug, don't do that again.
Okay.
Now get back to work.
The contents of the overturned
truck caught fire immediately,
but the driver was able to
escape with only minor injuries.
In Washington...
the President, at a
fund-raising event,
reiterated his desire to...
Come in. Close the door.
Provision he recommended
only weeks ago.
The President proposed
to cut the capital gains tax...
The latest audience research.
Diane's ratings are
sinking like the Titanic.
Modified so that upper income...
Maybe if we team her up with
somebody young and fresh.
Dump her.
She's been with the
station more than 12 years.
Well, you're going to have
to sooner or later, Howard.
Get some new blood. Dump her.
A woman her age in this
business... What's she going to do?
If there's one thing this lady
knows how to do, it's land on her feet.
Locally, after a
three-day hiatus,
the zoning commission
reassembles tomorrow.
When it convenes,
the commission will consider rezoning
an eight-mile stretch of farmland
located between state route
96 and McKenzie Highway
to allow for the development of
high-density, multi-family dwellings.
I can no longer sit idly by and watch
as thousands of my fellow citizens
fall victim to political inertia,
ineptitude, and just plain apathy.
I, therefore, hereby declare
that as of this moment
I seek to be the next
duly-elected representative
of the 11th Congressional
District of the great state of Georgia.
Anybody have any questions?
- Mr. Bevins!
- Right here!
Will yours be a positive
or a negative campaign?
Well, let's just say I owe it to
the good citizens of this state
to do whatever it takes
to beat the incumbent.
- Here.
- Yes.
How do you respond
to the charges
the Atlanta Nature Society
has leveled against you?
The Atlanta Nature Society?
They released a statement today
charging you with being anti-environment.
That's ridiculous. If anything, I'm
just the opposite. Next question.
It's right here in their
press release, Mr. Bevins.
They say you're so deeply indebted
to big business and heavy industry
that you can't possibly
address environmental issues
with any degree of objectivity.
Mr. Finley, that is slander.
I'm simply repeating what
is in this press release.
Everyone in this
room got one of these.
You've been had again, Billy.
- Mr. Bevins?
- Mr. Bevins!
Are you happy now? I'm fired.
I had nothing to do
with that press release.
The hell you didn't. You dummied
it up and left it on my desk.
It was somebody
else this time, not me.
Yeah, Doug.
Well, just remember, what
goes around comes around.
Doug, can I see you a minute?
Scout's honor, Howard. I had
nothing to do with that Bevins fiasco.
Good. The last thing I want is to
have to fire someone else around here.
If the kid had just
made one phone call,
he'd have known that that
press release was a phony.
But, as usual, he just barged straight
ahead without checking his facts.
I know. I know. That's not what
I wanted to talk to you about.
I just got a call from the
zoning commissioner.
We got our facts wrong on
a story we aired last night...
The one about the proposed rezoning
of some farmland south of Route 96.
We said the property goes all
the way to McKenzie Highway.
It doesn't.
Is that a big deal?
It is to Nelson Addleson.
He owns that property, and it
quadrupled in value overnight.
- Wow.
- A bunch of speculators snapped it up.
Addleson made a killing, which
really fried the commissioner's frijoles.
He hates Nelson Addleson's guts.
Well, I don't know how it
happened, but I'll find out.
Do that.
And run a correction and an apology
at the top of tonight's broadcast.
You got it.
It won't be ready by
the broadcast tonight.
They're working on
it down in Studio 7.
Got it.
You, my lady, are
about to get canned.
I figured. My numbers are down.
Did Howard tell you?
Yeah, Howard.
He knows about the little gaffe
you made on the air last night.
The zoning commissioner called.
And he's found out about the
killing that Nelson's making.
He wants us to broadcast
a correction ASAP.
- Are we going to?
- In a day or two.
The longer we wait, the
more money we make.
I did what you said... set up two
accounts at the Royal Bank of Bermuda.
Down there, you are now known as
Kevin Galloway, and I'm Vicky Davis.
Cute.
How are you going
to explain the gaffe?
One of our writers
got his facts wrong.
It happens all the time.
I hope we get away with it.
Hey, you're the one that
cut yourself in on this deal.
Yeah. When I found out
what you two were up to,
I'm sure I should have just
blown the whistle on you then.
Hey, come on.
Unemployment can
be fun if you're rich.
Nelson.
Nelson, no, you listen to me.
Now, we've stalled long enough.
Okay, one more
day, but that's it.
Not that fellow who
interviewed me the other day?
No, no, no. That was
Bill Finley. I fired him.
Why? Because of that
Rocky Bullwinkle business?
I fired him because there's
so much air between his ears,
- it's a wonder he doesn't float away.
- Hmm.
I'm talking about the
producer, Doug Levitt.
Oh. Here.
Thank you.
- Popcorn?
- No.
It's good. From a
health food store.
No.
Moves everything around.
So what did this...
What's his name?
- Levitt.
- Levitt. What did he do?
Two nights ago, we aired a story
that made it sound like some
worthless land was about to be rezoned
for a big residential
development.
As it turns out, the
story wasn't true.
But in the meantime, the
value of the land quadrupled,
and Nelson Addleson made a
fortune selling it to speculators.
I think Doug falsified the story because
he and Nelson Addleson are in cahoots.
Can you prove that?
That's why I'm
here. You tell me.
Today I overheard part of
a telephone conversation
between Doug Levitt
and Nelson Addleson,
so I checked Doug's
car phone bills.
The station pays them,
so he always turns them in.
Huh.
Kind of foolish... Dumb if
he's up to something, isn't it?
Look at that... nine calls in the
past two weeks to Nelson Addleson.
So can I nail the little
weasel to the wall or what?
Did you talk to him?
No.
Why don't you talk to him? Maybe
he's got a logical explanation.
Sit down.
What's the nature of your
relationship to Nelson Addleson?
I don't have a relationship
with Nelson Addleson.
You never see him?
You never talk to him?
No. Why would I?
You're fired, Doug.
I want your desk cleared
out by the end of the day.
- Wait a minute...
- I may press charges, I may not,
depending upon
what the attorneys say.
But in any case, you just looked
me straight in the eye and lied to me.
I won't have liars working
for me. Now get out.
Hey, Doug?
You look awful.
What happened?
I got the ax.
Ah, coffee.
Did it have anything to
do with Nelson Addleson?
Yeah. Yeah. Howard found out.
Oh, my God.
Not about you...
at least not yet.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Well, Howard might
decide to press charges.
If I stand trial, anything
might come out.
What is that?
Some kind of threat?
No, of course not. It's
just a statement of fact.
Besides, what do you care?
All this was about
to end anyway.
Or were you just worried
about your money?
Well, aren't you?
What's this?
Uh, it was mixed in with all the
stuff I brought home from work.
I don't know where it came from.
You played that
trick on Bill Finley.
No, I didn't.
Practical jokes aren't
my style, and you know it.
Uh-huh.
Well, I'd get out
of town for a while,
but I don't want to give Nelson
an excuse not to pay me my cut.
Well, I could go to Nelson and ask
him for your share as well as my own
and then wire it
to you in Bermuda.
No. No. First I get my money,
then I get out of the country.
Then why can't I meet you
somewhere and give it to you there?
Your cottage at Sidney Lake?
- When?
- Tuesday afternoon.
3.
Thank you, Diane.
I appreciate it.
Would you mind turning around?
What?
I just want to get a look at
you. Please, take off your hat.
You a cop?
Would you take off your hat?
How'd you like to make a couple
of hundred bucks for doing nothing?
Yeah.
Good evening, everyone.
At the top of tonight's news,
a story that has sent shockwaves
through the local broadcasting community.
Doug Levitt, former producer of the
5:00 News Hour here at WDRN-TV
died earlier this
afternoon in an explosion
that destroyed his
cottage at Sidney Lake.
Police have just identified
the charred remains
found at the scene
through dental records
and by tracing jewelry
the victim was wearing.
They say it appears that the explosion
was the result of a remote-controlled bomb,
which means they are
treating this case as a homicide.
The police have
arrested Bill Finley,
a former station employee
who was fired last week.
Bail will be set at $200,000.
Please see the cashier on the
second floor of the West Wing.
Where am I supposed
to get $200,000?
It will be taken care of.
You're paying for my
lawyer and my bail?
It's as clear as the nose on
my face you're innocent, Bill.
And I feel like this is all my fault. If I
hadn't fired you, you wouldn't be here.
Next case.
The People vs. Callahan...
What do you think?
Well, I've got my
work cut out for me.
I mean, the police found that
detonator in your garbage can.
Anybody could
have put that there.
Yeah. And the tire tracks
at the scene didn't help.
Come on, a lot of people
drive the same kind of car I do.
If you had an alibi, it would
help. That's all I'm saying.
I told you, I was at
home working on a book
that is going to blow
the lid off this town.
You uncovered some
corruption in Atlanta?
Well, I'm working on it.
What's next?
Well, I guess I'll go
see Nelson Addleson.
- Let's go.
- No.
No, no, no, no.
You go home and stay there.
Ben, I want to question him.
No. No. Right?
Go home and work on your book.
Go.
Are you sure you won't
join me, Mr. Matlock?
It isn't just any scotch...
Flintrock. It's over 40 years old.
Oh, no, thanks.
That stuff all tastes
like lighter fluid to me.
So what is this about?
Well, it's about all
those phone calls
Doug Levitt made to
you just before he died.
Is there a law against
calling a friend?
You and he were friends?
Yes.
He told Howard Price
he didn't know you.
Really?
I wonder why he did that.
Howard's sure that it
had something to do
with that false information
broadcast on Doug Levitt's news show.
You know, that stuff about all
that farmland south of Route 96
that was supposedly
up for rezoning.
Yeah, of course.
The station made a mistake,
and you made a killing.
Yeah. Well, what
was I supposed to do?
This is America. If something
like that happens, you go with it.
Yeah.
So Doug Levitt's phone
calls had nothing to do with it.
No, of course not.
What are you trying to say?
That he and I were some
kind of co-conspirators?
I'm just trying to figure out
why he lied about knowing you.
With him gone, it's
anybody's guess.
You know, there's a fine line
between speculation and libel,
and my lawyers,
they know where it is.
Yeah, I imagine they do.
But since I'm so close
to that fine line anyhow,
how about telling me where
you were the afternoon he died?
I was with a woman
named Jody Pfeiffer.
Here's her phone number.
I'd appreciate your
keeping that under your hat.
It wasn't exactly a business
meeting, and I'm not exactly single.
Oh.
You like walking
those fine lines, too.
Do you always run
through stop signs?
What stop sign?
Back there, 100 feet.
Where? Do you mind
if I get out of the car?
Just keep your hands
where I can see them, sir.
Where is it?
There's a bush in
front of that stop sign.
I didn't see it.
You can see enough of it.
How much is that ticket?
Sixty-one dollars.
Sign here, please.
That stop sign's
obscured. I won't pay it.
That's up to you,
sir. Pay it or fight it.
Sign here.
Only eight days to
prepare my case?
Prepare your ca...
You're going to a
lot of trouble for $61.
It's the principle.
Sure.
Finally. Come on in.
What's up?
Look at this.
Somebody found it in Diane
Becker's office this morning.
I don't understand.
Somebody found this in here?
Mr. Price's assistant found it when
she dropped the ratings off this morning.
I don't know anything about it.
It kind of looks like you pulled that prank
on Bill Finley, knowing he'd be fired.
Oh. No, I did no such thing.
I hate practical
jokes. Ask anybody.
Well, maybe you
didn't do it as a joke.
Maybe you did it
knowing for sure
that Bill would be fired and would
automatically blame Doug Levitt.
What are you saying?
That I tried to frame him?
That I really killed Doug?
I'm just commenting
on the way things look.
I'm busy trying to make an
honest living here. All right?
How about the afternoon of the
murder? Were you busy then?
I was right here editing
copy. Again, just ask anybody.
Okay.
Uh, was your door
open or closed?
Closed.
- Diane faked that press release?
- Maybe.
Diane doesn't play practical jokes.
That's the only thing I like about her.
Maybe it wasn't
a practical joke.
Maybe she knew you'd get
fired and blow up at Doug Levitt.
Maybe she was setting you up.
You mean Diane killed Doug?
Did she have any reason?
Not that I know of. They
seemed to get along.
What now?
Well, I'll go over
to Doug's place
and see if I can dig up some
connection between the two of them.
I'll go with you.
Let me get my stuff.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
I know you've got that magnifying
glass and fingerprint set and stuff, Bill,
but you'd better
work on your book.
Somebody framed me, Ben.
You don't expect me to just
sit on my thumbs, do you?
Yeah.
What I don't understand
is why a bomb?
Why didn't she just shoot him?
She's trying to
frame Bill Finley.
What does he know about
explosives? He's no rocket scientist.
He's lucky enough to
come in out of the rain.
Well, he did a story on
some local demolition experts
who hire out to the mob when
they're not doing construction.
When was that?
It never happened. They
didn't have any proof.
- Got caught in the rain again, huh?
- Yeah.
But the police think that Bill Finley hired
one of those guys to bomb Doug Levitt.
Poor sucker.
Well, Diane knew about the story.
It could just as easily have been her.
What's Rapamune?
Blood pressure medicine.
A lot of people take that.
Now what?
Well, we figure out which
demolition expert made that bomb
and get him to say who
hired him in open court.
Diane, how nice.
Sit down, Nelson.
Problems, Diane?
Somebody's trying to
frame me for Doug's murder.
Diane, come on. They
arrested Bill Finley.
Who would want to frame you?
I don't know, but somebody does.
Ben Matlock came to see me.
Yeah, me, too.
And he got nowhere.
Relax.
I want my money, Nelson.
You'll get it.
I want it by the
end of the week.
And I want Doug's cut, too.
Excuse me?
Doug's cut.
Or what? You'll
go to the police?
You truly are out of your mind.
I don't like being
framed, Nelson.
If that money isn't in my
account in Bermuda by Friday...
you're not going to
like it much, either.
N-No, Conrad. Not from there.
You can see the
sign fine from there.
You've got to get
back where I was.
You're too close. You've
got to get farther in the street.
I can see the sign fine.
You want to shoot this yourself?
Just back up. Just
back... back on up.
Just back... back up
till... Okay. Go on, back.
Back, back, back.
- Back up.
- Whoa!
Did you hurt yourself?
Sure I hurt myself. You
think I fell down for fun?
Rub it a little. You'll recover.
- You're not hurt that bad.
- How do you know?
I'm a doctor.
How much did it cost?
None of your business.
Well why are you going
through all this trouble anyway?
I told you, it's the principle.
The 8-year-old was wounded
when a bullet passed through the
open window of the car driving by
and struck him in the chest.
He was taken to Children's Hospital
and is in satisfactory condition.
None of the gang members involved
in the incident have been apprehended.
When we return, a look at the early morning
fire that destroyed an Atlanta landmark.
Stay with us.
And we're clear.
30 seconds, people.
Where's that new copy?
Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
- How's it going, Diane?
- Hi, Bill. How are you doing?
Not too well, actually. Being
framed for murder is real pain.
- Why did you do it anyway?
- What are you talking about, Bill?
Fifteen seconds.
I know about that press release,
Diane. What I want to know is why.
Bill, I did not dummy
up that release.
I don't know what to know is what
that form was doing in my office.
Stop lying, okay? Why
did you kill him, Diane?
What was going on
between you two?
- Somebody please get him out of here.
- 10 seconds.
I'm not leaving here
until I get the truth.
Get your hands off of me.
- Five seconds.
- For God's sakes, get Howard!
Somebody, get... Two seconds.
The Peachtree Museum was
the scene of a three-alarm fire
which broke out about
4:30 this morning.
You're right on time.
- Do you like my suit?
- Yeah.
- Everything under control?
- Yes, it is.
Yeah, Ben, I followed
Addleson down to Southgate.
Something's going on.
Okay, I've got to go.
Gentlemen, it's payday.
Ha ha! Yeah! Give it up,
then, Reg. What's up, man?
- I've been waiting for this.
- Give it up, man.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Thank you, y'all.
They know I had to be paid.
All I want to know is what they
were saying before it worked.
- They know I had to be paid.
- Uh-huh.
Oye.
- What's up, man?
- Hey, hey, hey.
Shut up.
- Don't be stupid, man.
- Yo, what's up, man?
My brother got cut last night.
Did he say it was us?
He can't. You cut his throat.
It wasn't us.
I say it was.
Wait a minute. He didn't kill
nobody. He was in jail last night.
Everybody knew that, right?
What's up, man?
He was in there, man.
If my brother dies,
one of you dies.
- Yeah, right.
- The exact same way.
Yo, man, what's
the problem, man?
Ben, guess what I found out.
Howard Price called.
Didn't I tell you
I'd handle this?
- Yes.
- Then why did you down to that station
and make an even bigger jackass
out of yourself than you already are?
Ben, shut up.
She wasn't there.
Who wasn't where?
Diane wasn't in her office.
She doesn't have
an alibi after all.
Chinese food?
Yeah. Yeah.
You ordered Chinese food from your
office the afternoon Doug was killed,
but when the boy
tried to deliver it at
3:25, he couldn't
because you weren't there.
I did not order
Chinese food that day.
Yes, you did because one of the fellows
that works down at the station remembers
because when you weren't
there to accept the delivery, he did.
Mr. Matlock, if I did, as you
contend, slip out of my office
so I could drive up to Sidney
Lake and blow Doug to smithereens,
why in God's name would I
have ordered Chinese food?
Well, my guess is that you figured
you'd be back before it was delivered.
And if it had worked, it would
have been a good idea, but it didn't.
I've got to get ready for work.
Here's your paper.
Thank you very much.
Oh, and your subpoena.
Yeah.
How are you?
I didn't mean to scare you.
Who are you?
Conrad McMasters.
I work for Ben
Matlock, the attorney.
I want to ask you
some questions.
About?
Do you mind my asking
what you're working on there?
A birdhouse.
In view of how you make your living,
you can understand why I had to ask.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm investigating the explosion
that killed Doug Levitt last week,
and I have reason to believe that
you're the one that rigged the bomb.
The police have
already been here.
They didn't get anywhere,
and neither will you.
Yeah, but they don't
know who hired you. I do...
Diane Becker.
Never heard of her.
I understand usually in these
jobs you just blow up property,
but here somebody died.
You're talking
about an accident.
I'm talking about murder.
What? Diane didn't tell you
that somebody was in that
cottage when you blew it up?
Nobody's ever died in any of
your explosions before, Mr. Krauss.
She lied to you, didn't she?
I don't know what you're talking
about, and that's all I'm going to say.
Now get out.
Hello.
You were right.
She did lie to me.
The more I think about
it, the madder I get.
So you listen up.
I'm listening.
I didn't push the
button. She did.
I always do it that way.
I rig the explosives, and I
order a detonator from a buddy.
The client picks
it up and uses it.
It's safer for me that way.
Now I'm going to give you my
buddy's name, and I'm going to hang up.
Then I'm going
on a long vacation.
All right. Hang on.
Go ahead.
Uh, do you recognize
this, Ms. Becker?
Of course. It's the device that
triggered the bomb that killed Doug Levitt.
The police found it
in Mr. Finley's garage.
I watched the assistant
D.A. enter it into evidence.
Did you see it before that?
No, of course not.
No?
Isn't this the device you
bought from Jake Lubenthal?
Excuse me?
You do know Jake
Lubenthal, don't you?
I've never heard of him.
Well, he knows you.
Well, a lot of people know
me whom I don't know.
Well, he does.
Jake, stand up.
There. See? Recognize him now?
No.
The reason I keep asking is that he
had a long talk with the judge this morning
and with the assistant
district attorney,
and he's been granted immunity.
And that means when he
comes up here and testifies
that he sold you this
detonator on March 25th,
just two days before the murder,
he won't be prosecuted
as an accessory.
You bought this
from Jake Lubenthal
and used it to set off the bomb
that was made by Trevor Krauss.
You murdered Doug
Levitt, didn't you?
Your Honor, uh, I'd just as soon
not answer any more questions
until I've spoken
with my attorney.
I object, Your Honor. She's
been sworn to tell the truth.
Please direct her to
answer my question.
Overruled, Mr. Matlock.
The witness is entitled
to confer with counsel.
This court will reconvene
tomorrow morning at 9:00 a.m.
I'm a busy man. This
had better be good.
One of your guys
shot an 8-year-old kid.
Accident. It happens.
This is the first and
the last accident.
Injured bystanders
attract too much attention.
Okay.
No more gunplay.
Okay!
Still running that
scam with Reggie, huh?
That's good. You're in
business, I'm in business.
I don't know what the
hell you're talking about.
Doug?
That's right.
Man, they found your body.
No, just some poor old bum.
You screwed up, Nelson.
What do you mean?
You don't expect me to believe that
Diane set me up all by herself, do you?
Diane tried to kill you?
I want my cut of that land
deal, and I want it now.
I haven't got it. I
gave it to Diane.
Why did you do that?
Because she said she'd go to
the cops if I didn't give it to her.
That's okay.
Diane's taken care of.
What do you mean?
I've been making her sweat.
The cops will nail
her for my murder.
I've been leaving little clues.
You're the one?
Yeah, I thought the Chinese
food was a nice touch.
What are you, an idiot? If
she goes down, we all go down.
I thought you were in on this
killing me business with Diane.
- Are you stupid?
- It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
It's okay.
I'll fix it.
He'll fix it.
Oh, man.
- Diane.
- Oh!
Doesn't death become me?
No! No! No! No!
When I saw those blank press releases
from the Atlanta Nature Society in here,
I started to follow you.
No! Ow!
And when you met with that
guy at the construction site,
I remembered that story we
investigated about the demolition scam.
And suddenly it hit me, you
wanted me to meet you at the cottage
so you could blow
me to kingdom come.
Well, I hate to tell you, Diane,
but the guy you killed was
just some poor old drifter.
I'm still very much alive.
What are you going to do?
Well, the thing is, Diane,
back then I was very angry with
you, so I started setting you up.
Do you remember
the Chinese food?
The blank press
releases in your office?
That was you?
Yeah.
But I made a mistake, Diane.
I forgot that the trail leads
from you to Nelson Addleson.
And now that I'm dead, Nelson's
my sole source of support.
If you talk, he goes
down, and so do I.
I swear to God, I won't talk.
I won't say a word.
- Really? Really, Diane?
- Yeah.
- I can trust you?
- You can trust me. You can trust me.
I wish I could believe
that, but I don't.
So you're going
to commit suicide.
No one will hear you.
It won't be bad.
Oh, God, no! No! No!
No!
Sweet dreams, Diane.
www.tvsubtitles.net